# GREG MUNRO

Front-end Developer

## **DETAILS**

#### **PHONE**

+34 622 568 805

#### **EMAIL**

gregmunro90@gmail.com

## LINKS

**Portfolio** 

**Github** 

LinkedIn

# **SKILLS**

React

JavaScript

CSS3

HTML5

Git

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Spanish

## **PROFILE**

Front-end Developer, living in Barcelona since 2016 with previous experience in Music and Customer Service. In 2020 I decided to change career paths due to the pandemic and follow my interest in Web Development. In December 2021, I proudly graduated from Ironhack Barcelona, after an intensive 3 month web development bootcamp.

During this time, I learnt to create one page applications using React, API, Node.js, Express, Mongoose, MongoDB CSS3, HTML5, Tailwind, Bootstrap and Javascript. Before this, professional experiences were in music-licensing, publishing and a strong customer service with Netflix and Toyota.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## International Copyright Coordinator, Concord Music Publishing

London

Jan 2021 — Oct 2021

- Implement copyright d across Pop, Jazz and Media catalogs, administrating copyright data of over 260,000 works, bulk registering copyright data via CWR, ingesting sub-publisher data.
- Maintained royalty databases, database population, new works and agreements registration across 5 continents.
- Liaised with PRS/MCPS, ICE and international societies on all matters relating to works and catalogs
- Resolution of duplicate claims and conflicts at performance and mechanical rights organisations.

#### **Booking Agent, Analog**

Barcelona

Jan 2019 — Mar 2020

- Tour schedule management of 6 high profile, international electronic musical artists
- Negotiated performance contracts with promoters, venues and festivals worldwide
- Facilitate logistical assistants with touring administration, visa processing and legal assets

# Logistics & Tour Administration Assistant, B4 Bookings

Barcelona

Nov 2016 — Nov 2018

- Global logistics manager for 45 touring electronic music artists
- · Issued contracts, invoices, itineraries, performance visas
- Booked travel, diary, and crew management for worldwide tours for 500+ events per year
- Uploaded and maintained records of contractual, logistical, accounting info onto a bespoke system, overseeing team of 8 assistants

### **EDUCATION**

### Full Stack Web Development, Ironhack

Barcelona

Oct 2021 — Jan 2022

React, Javascript (ES6), MongoDB, Express, Node, HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Bootstrap, API

# Music Supervision & Licensing, Berklee College of Music

Remote

Mar 2020 — Sep 2020

# BMus (hons) Music Performance, University Of West London

London

Sep 2009 — Sep 2012